Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Service, 1970s-2015
  - Conferences, Consulting, and Organizations, 1970s-2015; 1
    - US Council of Economic Advisors - Civilian Technology, 1961-1962 (Box 58)
      Files related to serving on panel for CEA
    - USSR Institute of Control Sciences, 1988 (Box 64)
    - V., Misc., 1995-1999 (Box 28)
    - Veblen-Clark Lecture, 1993 (Box 28)
      Presentation "Information as an Economic Good" given at Carleton College, Northfield, MN
    - Waseda Talk, undated (Box 28)
      Presentation on "Social and Economic Values and Obligations"
    - WDR, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Weitzman Institute Dinner, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Western Economic Association - Nominating Committee, 1986 (Box 64)
    - Western Economic Association: International, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Western Economic Association: San Francisco, 1992 (Box 28)
      Files for panel discussion "The Future of the Nation-State"
    - Western Michigan Talk, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
      Talk on "The State of Economic Science" given at Western Michigan University, Kalamazoo, MI
    - Wharton Risk Center, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 58)
      Files related to serving on Wharton Risk and Decision Processes Center Advisory Committee
    - Wharton Risk Center, 1985-1986 (Box 64)
    - WIDER (World Institute for Development Economics Research), 1983-1991 (Box 58)
      Files related to consulting for World Institute for Development Economics Research
    - Williams College Lecture, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Williamson Organization Conference, 1991 (Box 28)
      Presentation on "Scale Returns in Communication and Elite Control of Organizations"
    - WINE (Workshop on Internet and Network Economics), 2007 (Box 28)
      Presentation on history of general equilibrium given at 3rd International Workshop on Internet and Network Economics
    - Wisdom Toward the 21st Century, 1983 (Box 28)
      Presentation on "The International Economic Order of the 21st Century" given at Symposium in Osaka, Japan
    - Witten Lecture, 2007 (Box 58)
      Files for presentation on anti-malaria drugs given at Cambridge, UK
    - Witten Lectures, 2009 (Box 28)
    - World Bank Talk, 2008 (Box 28)
      Talk on "Climate Change and Deep-Future Disasters"
    - World Bank: Braverman, 1988 (Box 58)
      Correspondence related to Public Risk Aversion
    - World Bank: Malaria, 2011 (Box 58)
      Files related to anti-malarial drug subsidy program
    - World Congress Environment, 2002 (Box 28)
      Presentation on "Some Paradoxes of Sustainability" at World Congress of Environmental and Resource Economists
    - World Health Organization, 1986 (Box 28)
      Invitation to give keynote address at special program for Research and Training in Tropical Diseases
    - World Resources Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 58)
      Files related to serving on advisory panel
    - Xiamen University, 2011 (Box 28)
      Files related to conference celebrating 90th anniversary of Xiamen University
    - Yahoo Talk, 2009 (Box 28)
      Presentation on "Discounting a Long and Uncertain Future" at Yahoo Research
    - Yale Global Health, 2011 (Box 28)
      Files related to seminar at Yale University
    - Yale Non-Profit Program, 1981-1989 (Box 58)
    - Yeshiva University - Brody Lecture, 2001 (Box 28)
      Lecture on "Responsibility to the Stranger: The Far-Away in Time and Place"
  - Engagements, 1978-2013; 2
    This subseries contains files and documentation of Arrow's speaking engagements.
    - Arrow Itineraries, 1991-2012; 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Engagements electronic records, 1999-2016; 55 files; less than 2 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Invitations Declined, 1979-2013; 14 folders (Box 29)
      Declined invitations
    - Invitations for Speaking, 1986-1991 (Box 29)
    - Invitations Refused, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Invitations Unaccepted, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Lectures - Invitations and Refusals, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
    - Pending Invitations, 1997 (Box 29)
  - Expert Witness, 1978-2010; 3
    Arrow acted as an expert witness in several court cases in the State of Calornia and nationally. Cases are arranged alphabetically and include trial transcripts, notes, testimony, and correspondence.
    - Asbestos Cases, 1985-1986; 5 folders (Box 59)
    - AT&T Case, 1982 (Box 59)
      Files for testimony on proposed FCC regulation of AT&T
    - Bell Atlantic - GTE, 1998; 2 folders (Box 59)
      Statement given on proposed merger between Bell Atlantic and GTE Corporation
    - Burlington, 2000 (Box 59)
      Statement given on behalf of Burlington Northern Santa Fe Corporation in relation to regulations on railroad consolidation
    - Chichilinsky vs Wooders, 1993-1996; 13 folders (Box 59)
      Files related to court case concerning misappropriation of ideas
    - Chichilinsky vs Wooders, 1991-2004; 4 folders (Box 60)
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1987 (Box 60)
    - Copper Case, 2001 (Box 60)
      Testimony given in copper market antitrust litigation
    - Cutler - Amicus Curige, 2010 (Box 60)
      Files related to supporting Affordable Care Act
    - DuPont Report, 1980 (Box 60)
      Commentary on handling of nuclear waste
    - Evergreen vs NCR Comten, 1985 (Box 60)
    - Expert Witness electronic records, 2005; 3 files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - FNMA, 1992 (Box 60)
      Report given in response to Federal National Mortgage Association v. Commissioner
    - IBM vs. Seagate, 1995 (Box 60)
    - LAX Airport Fee, 1995 (Box 60)
    - Litton vs Honeywell, 1997 (Box 60)
    - McDermott, 1986 (Box 60)
      Deposition for marine antitrust construction antitrust litigation
    - Microsoft Anti-Trust, 1994 (Box 60)
    - Orange County vs Merrill Lynch, 1998 (Box 60)
    - Pharmaceutical Anti-Trust, 1995 (Box 60)
    - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1985 (Box 60)
      Testimony on alternatives to the valuation of natural gas
    - Polypropylene Anti-Trust, 1999 (Box 60)
    - Railroad Cases, 1986 (Box 60)
    - RBOC Mfg., 1991 (Box 60)
      Comments on proposed legislation regulating telecommunications equipment
    - San Francisco Foundation, 1985 (Box 60)
    - Shell Oil vs Travelers Insurance, 1987 (Box 60)
    - SPCC vs AT&T, 1982 (Box 60)
    - Steel Imports, 1993 (Box 60)
      Files related consulting on import duties related to steel production
    - Sun vs Microsoft, 1998 (Box 60)
    - Telecommunications Regulation, 1984 (Box 60)
    - Trans-Alaska Pipeline, 1978-1983; 3 folders (Box 60)
    - US Air vs American and United, 1988; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - US vs Microsoft, 2002 (Box 61)
    - US vs Western Electric and AT&T, 1991 (Box 61)
    - Verizon, 2003 (Box 61)
    - Williams Pipeline, 1979; 2 folders (Box 61)
      Testimony given before Federal Energy Regulation Commission
  - Politics and Activism, 1974-2012; 4
    Contains files documenting Arrow's personal and political activities. Notable topics include his work for peace in the Middle East, for arms control, and in support of human rights and dissidents.
    - ACLU, 1980-2002 (Box 61)
    - Air Quality, 1998 (Box 61)
    - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East, 1977-1990; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Baky Forum, 2012 (Box 61)
    - Balanced Budget Amendment, 1982-1997 (Box 61)
    - Beyond War, 1987-1991 (Box 61)
      Files related to efforts for peace in the Middle East
    - Brown for Governor, 1994 (Box 61)
    - Center for International Security and Arms Control, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Childright Initiative, 1994 (Box 61)
      Files related to Nobel Prizewinners Initiative to Stop Child Exploitation
    - Coalition for a Comprehensive Test Ban, 1993 (Box 61)
    - Committee for Concerned Scientists, 1981-1987 (Box 61)
      Files related human rights activism
    - Committee for International Academic Freedom, 1992 (Box 61)
    - Croatia, 1991 (Box 61)
      Files related to appeals for peace in Croatia
    - ECAAR (Economists Against the Arms Race), 1987-2005; 9 folders (Box 61)
      Files related to conference, presentations, and serving as co-chair of board
    - ECAAR, 1991-1993; 4 folders (Box 62)
    - ECAAR: Haifa Conference, 1994 (Box 62)
    - ECAAR: Kashmir, 1994 (Box 62)
    - ECAAR: Notre Dame, 1990-1991 (Box 62)
    - ECAAR: Nuclear Statement, 2002 (Box 62)
    - ECAAR: Russia, 1998 (Box 62)
    - Economics of Arms and Disarmament, 1989-1991 (Box 61)
      Files for presentation on arms control
    - Economics of Arms Reduction, 1991-1993 (Box 61)
      Files related to technical report
    - EPS (Economists for Peace and Security), 2012 (Box 62)
      Files related to meeting of fellows and board
    - European Network, 2001 (Box 62)
      Files for serving as sponsor of European Network for Peace and Human Rights
    - Gardels Statement, 1999 (Box 62)
      Public statement on dangers of nuclear arms
    - Human Rights: Aurora Foundation, 1987 (Box 62)
      Files related to serving on foundation's Human Rights Committee
    - Human Rights: Baha'i, 1982-1983 (Box 62)
      Files related to advocating for members of Baha'i religion in Iran
    - Human Rights: Chile, 1976-1979 (Box 62)
      Files related to advocating for political prisoners
    - Human Rights: Dissidents, 1974-1991; 4 folders (Box 62)
      Correspondence related to advocating for persecuted scholars
    - Human Rights: El Salvador and Central America, 1984-1986 (Box 62)
    - Human Rights: Ida Nudel, 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 62)
      Correspondence related to advocating for the release of Ida Nudel from exile
    - Human Rights: South Africa, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, 1994 (Box 62)
    - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, 1988-1996; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Iraq Statement, 2003 (Box 62)
      Statement in opposition to war in Iraq
    - Israel Democracy Institute, 1990-1992 (Box 62)
    - Israel-Diaspora Institute, 1990 (Box 62)
    - Letelier, 1977 (Box 62)
      Letter to Pinochet advocating for release of Fernando Ortiz Letelier
    - Meiman, Naum, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
      Files related to advocating for Naum Meiman to be granted permission to leave Soviet Union
    - Middle East, 1973-1988 (Box 62)
      Files and correspondence related to advocating for peace in region
    - Middle East Policy, 1992 (Box 62)
    - Mid-East Center for Economic Development and Institutional Development, 1989-1990 (Box 62)
    - Minimum Wage Initiative, 1996 (Box 62)
    - Norwegian Climate Change, 2009-2010 (Box 62)
    - PCL (Planning and Conservation League) Initiative, 1998 (Box 62)
      Files related to Planning and Conservation League
    - Politics and Activism electronic records, 1999-2014; 19 files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Public Statements, 1994-2001 (Box 62)
    - Public Statements, 2002-2011; 4 folders (Box 63)
    - Redefining Progress, 1997 (Box 63)
      Files related to statements on climate change
    - Scholars for Peace, 2005 (Box 63)
    - Sunstein Nomination, 2009 (Box 63)
      Statement supporting Cass Sunstein's nomination to Administrator of the Office of Information and Regulatory Affairs
    - UNESCO, 1974-1978; 11 folders (Box 63)
      Files related to serving on U.S. National Commission for UNESCO
    - UNESCO: Council on Future, 1999-2003 (Box 63)
      Files related to serving as Council member
    - UNESCO: Delphi, 1986 (Box 63)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1982-1985 (Box 63)
      Files related to advocacy for arms control
- Research and Notes, 1939-2016 and undated
  Includes Arrow's notes and correspondence for research projects, notes from classes taken, and academic writings by others. Research notes include files on Arrow's collaboration with Frank Hahn, the uniqueness of equilibrium, production functions, and uncertainty, among other topics and files of hand-written notes. Arrow's class notes contain materials from courses taken with Harold Hotelling.
  - Research, 1953-2016 and undated; 1
    This subseries contains documents for Arrow's research projects, including his work with Frank Hahn, the uniqueness and stability of general equilibrium, optimal growth, production functions, and uncertainty.
    - Adverse Selection, undated (Box 37)
    - Advertising and Information, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Antibiotic Study, 2005-2007 (Box 37)
    - Arrow-Hahn Book, 1977 (Box 37)
    - Arrow-Hahn Plans for Revisions, 1977 (Box 37)
    - Arrow-Hahn Siena, 1998; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Arrow-Hahn Stability, 1988-1989 (Box 37)
    - Arrow SFI, 1996; 11 files derived from floppy disk, 1.4 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
      Includes file related to research projects.
    - Borda and PR, 1999 (Box 37)
    - Classical Famine, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Comments on Arrow Lecture, 2016 (Box 37)
    - Competition and R&D Portfolio, 2004; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Conflict of Values, undated (Box 37)
    - Cournot Oligopoly, 1979 (Box 37)
    - Current Thoughts, undated (Box 37)
    - Debreu-Kirman, 1997 (Box 37)
    - Decentralization, 1976-1978; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Demand for Supplementary Health Insurance, 1974 (Box 37)
    - Discounting, 2014 (Box 37)
    - Discounting Climate Change, undated (Box 37)
    - Duopoly, 1975 (Box 37)
    - Dynamic Monopoly Pricing (Exhaustive), undated (Box 37)
    - Dynamic Systems, undated (Box 37)
    - Economics of Information, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Economy of Israel, 1984 (Box 37)
    - Employment Security, undated (Box 37)
    - Energy, 1973-1974 (Box 37)
      Notes related to issues of nuclear power
    - Equilibrium Optimality, 1960-1968 (Box 37)
    - Equilibrium, uniqueness, 1953-1964 (Box 37)
      Includes notes, reference materials, related correspondence
    - Excerpt from the Collected Mathematical Papers of Arthus Cayley, undated (Box 37)
    - Exhaustible Resources, undated (Box 37)
    - Experimental Economics, 2016 (Box 37)
    - Granger Reprints, 1963-1967 (Box 37)
    - Handbook - Sweeney, 1990 (Box 37)
      Notes related to Handbook of Natural Resource and Energy Economics
    - Health Capital, 2013 (Box 37)
    - Inflation, 1974 (Box 37)
    - Information, misc., 1987-1996 (Box 37)
    - Innovation in Multi-national Firms, 2015 (Box 37)
    - Intergenerational Equity, undated (Box 37)
    - Learning by Doing and Specialization, undated (Box 37)
    - Limit on Network and Wages, 2004 (Box 37)
    - Malaria Drugs, undated (Box 37)
    - Longevity, 2012-2013 (Box 37)
    - Maximization Under Chaos, undated (Box 37)
    - M-Matrix Stability, undated (Box 37)
    - Network Connection and Wage Distribution, 2001 (Box 37)
    - Nonlinear Bertrand Pricing, undated (Box 37)
    - Nonlinear Metzler System, undated (Box 37)
    - Notes/Plots for Simple Two-Period Model with Random Productivity, undated (Box 37)
    - Notes on Ramsey Model, undated (Box 37)
    - Old Manuscripts, 1997 (Box 37)
      Unsorted hand-written notes
    - Oligopoly with Nonlinear Pricing, 1998 (Box 37)
    - OPEC Pricing: Demand Reduction, undated (Box 37)
    - Optimal Growth, 1965-1967 (Box 37)
    - Optimal Growth in Linear Models, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Optimal Retirement, undated (Box 37)
    - Optimization and Decentralization, 1950-1960 (Box 37)
    - Organization Theory Group, 1972 (Box 37)
    - Permanent Income as Welfare, 1990 (Box 37)
    - Precautionary Principle, 2000-2003 (Box 37)
    - Production Functions: Bibliography, 1969 (Box 37)
    - Production Functions: CES Fits, 1966 (Box 37)
      Includes notes, correspondence, and references
    - Production Functions: Cheney-Solow Proposal, 1965-1970 (Box 37)
    - Production Functions: Elasticities, undated (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: Embodiment, 1962-1966 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: Learning by Doing, 1962-1968 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: Murata, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: NSF Production Proposal, 1960-1964 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: NSF Reporting, 1964-1965 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: Non-neutral Progress, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: Relations to Growth Models, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Production Functions: Statistical Method, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Quadratic Voting, 2015 (Box 38)
    - Racial Discrimination, undated (Box 38)
    - Rate of Discount on Public Investments w/Imperfect Capital Markets, undated (Box 38)
    - Research electronic records, 1999-2016; 27 files; 18 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Rubin Project, 1979 (Box 38)
      Notes for project on uncertainty in energy planning
    - Scarf-Fixed Point, undated (Box 38)
    - Search, Equilibrium and Information, 1974 (Box 38)
    - Search for Maximum: Stopping Short, undated (Box 38)
    - Smith Comment, 1990 (Box 38)
      Notes on Vernon Smith's work
    - Social Choice Correspondence and Notes, 1974-1977 (Box 38)
    - Socialist Reform, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 38)
      Includes notes and reference materials
    - Spatial Allocation of Non-Educational Public Expenditure, Public Invest for Optimal Development, undated (Box 38)
    - Stability, 1956-1965; 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Tax Reform, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
    - Technology Assessment, 1977 (Box 38)
    - Transparencies, undated (Box 38)
      Uncategorized transparencies and lecture slides
    - Uncertainty, 1963-1966; 4 folders (Box 38)
      Includes notes, correspondence, and reference materials
    - Uncertainty in Energy Planning, 1979; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Unspecificity of Knowledge, undated (Box 38)
    - Value of Future Life, undated (Box 38)
    - Value of Life, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - VC Questionnaire Paper, 1996 (Box 38)
    - Wages by Auction, 2001 (Box 38)
    - World Sustainability, 2006 (Box 38)
    - World Sustainability II, 2007 (Box 38)
    - Misc. Hand-written Notes, undated; 7 folders (Box 39)
      Uncategorized hand-written notes
    - Misc. Notes, 1981; 3 folders (Box 39)
      Uncategorized hand-written notes and references
  - Class Notes, 1939-1966 and undated; 2
    Includes notes and other materials from classes taken by Arrow.
    - Current Types of Economic Theory, 1941-1942 (Box 42)
    - Economics of Social Insurance (Actuarial basis of Unemployment Insurance and Mathematical Economics (with Harold Hotelling)), undated (Box 42)
    - Educational Psychology (Mexican Civilization), undated (Box 42)
    - Honors Essays (Quaternions and Mathematical Statistics), 1939-1940 (Box 42)
    - Notes - Meteorology, undated (Box 42)
    - Philosophy Classes (Nature of Mathematics, Consistency of a Mathematical System), 1939 (Box 42)
    - "Reorganizing the Maximum of a Sequence" by Gilbert and Mosteller, 1966 (Box 42)
    - "Stochastic Processes" (Master's Thesis), 1940 (Box 42)
    - Theory of Functions (Jordan Separation Theorem and Prime Number Theorem), 1940-1941 (Box 42)
  - Writings by Others, 1960-2008; 3
    Contains scholarly and popular writings by others that served as part of Arrow's resources for his research activities.
    - Writings by Others: A-F, 1963-2008; 12 folders (Box 43)
    - Writings by Others: F-K, 1960-2008; 13 folders (Box 44)
    - Writings by Others: L-R, 1966-2008; 12 folders (Box 45)
    - Writings by Others: R-Z, 1966-2008; 13 folders (Box 46)
    - Writings by Others electronic records, 2005-2016; 200 files; 148 MB. (Digital-materials Unknown)
- Writings, 1950-2017
  This series contains copies, reprints, drafts, notes, and other documents associated with Arrow's published works. These include: reprints and copies of published journal articles and book chapters; copies of his books, including translated versions; contributions to festschrfit volumes; and documents from his referee activity for academic journals and publishers.
  - Articles and Chapters, 1950-2017 and undated; 1
    Contains copies, reprints, and drafts of Arrow's published journal articles and chapters contributed to edited volumes.
    - 100 Years of the American Economic Review: The Top 20 Articles, 2011; 2 folders (Box 30)
      Original, related correspondence
    - Additive Logarithmic Demand Functions and the Slutsky Relations, 1961 (Box 30)
      Reprint, copy
    - Admissible Points of Convex Sets, 1953 (Box 30)
      Reprint
    - Allocation of Resources in Large Teams, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Allocation of Risk Bearing, undated (Box 40)
      Draft
    - Alternative Approaches to the Theory of Choice in Risk-Taking Situations, 1951 (Box 30)
    - Alternative Proof of the Substitution Theorem for Leontief Models in the General Case, 1951 (Box 30)
    - Amartya K. Sen's Contributions to the Study of Social Welfare, 1999 (Box 30)
    - Analysis and Evaluation of Public Expenditures, 1969 (Box 30)
      Copy
    - Antimalarial in Africa NEJM, 2005 (Box 30)
      Copy of paper "Making Antimalarial Agents Available in Africa"
    - Applications of Control Theory to Economic Growth, 1967 (Box 30)
      Copy, includes draft
    - Are We Consuming Too Much?, 2004 (Box 30)
    - Arrow Lectures vol. 1, 2012; 5 files derived from optical disk; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
      Includes draft writings and associated files.
    - Articles and Chapters electronic records, 2003-2016; 172 files; 107 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Basic Economics of Arms Reduction, 1992 (Box 30)
    - Bayes and Minimax Solutions of Sequential Decision Problem, 1949 (Box 30)
    - Benefit-Cost Analysis in Environmental, Health, and Safety Regulation, 1991 (Box 30)
      Original
    - Benefits of Education and the Formation of Preferences, 1997 (Box 30)
    - Beyond the Ivory Tower, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Bliss, Catastrophe, and Rational Policy, 2011-2014 (Box 40)
      Drafts
    - Bounded Rationality, 2004 (Box 30)
      Copy of contribution to memorial volume for Herbert Simon
    - Bulletin Sedeis, 1965 (Box 30)
      Reprint of paper titled "Connaissance, Productivite et Pratique"
    - Capitalism, for Better or Worse, 1974 (Box 30)
    - Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy, 2001 (Box 30)
      Copy of contribution to colloquium celebrating 50th anniversary of Schumpeter's book
    - Capital-Labor Substitutions and Economic Efficiency, 1961; 2 folders (Box 30)
      Reprint, includes Slovak translation
    - Case Studies, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Cautious Case for Socialism, 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 30)
      Copy, includes French translation
    - Certainty Equivalence and Inequivalence for Prices, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Chetterji Globalization Vol., 2000 (Box 40)
      Draft of "Globalization and its Implications for International Security"
    - Classificatory Notes on the Production and Transmission of Technological Knowledge, 1969 (Box 30)
    - Combination of Time Series and Cross-Section Data in Inter-industry Flow Analysis, 1974 (Box 30)
    - Comment on Cooper, 2000; 2 folders (Box 30)
      Reprint, copy of contribution to "World Bank Research Observer", proofs, related correspondence
    - Comment on Lazarsfeld Prize, 1979 (Box 30)
      Collected volume
    - Comment on M. Kurz, 1996 (Box 30)
      Copy of comment on "Rational Preferences and Rational Beliefs" by Mordecai Kurz
    - Comment on Women and the Workplace, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Comments in Cummings, Brookshire, Schulze, 1986 (Box 30)
      Copy of contribution to volume on "Valuing Environmental Goods: A State of the Art Assessment of the Contingent Valuation Method"
    - Comments on Chipman, 1990 (Box 30)
      Copy of contribution to "Models Incorporating Technology Factor"
    - Comments on Developing Countries and the New Financial Architecture, 2001 (Box 30)
      Copy of comments on piece by Griffith-Jones
    - Comments on Paul David, 2008 (Box 30)
      Copy of comment on "The Historical Origins of `Open Science'" by Paul David
    - Comments on the Commentaries, 1999 (Box 30)
      Copy of contribution to "Competition and Cooperation" by Alt, Levi, and Ostrom